Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence-Hare Family, 1724-1965
  - Charles (brother) to Emily, 1908 December 28; No. 2144
    Thank you for box of groceries. Account of Christmas activities (a luxurious visit to friends).
  - Molly to Miss E.B. Hare, 1908 December 28; No. 2145
    Thank you for Christmas telegram. (You were the "Ethel" it was signed weren't you?)
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 January 14; No. 2146
    Enjoyed being with you. About getting clothes. Going South. On your good fortune.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 February 8; No. 2147
    Esther, Hoffman and I had glorious time in Havana. Esther went to MacVeagh's. Description of camp.
  - Newspaper - The Philadelphia Press, 1909 February 21; No. 2148
    Article "A Victory in Peace Greater Than That of War Has Been Achieved by Globe-Girdling Cruise of Great Battle Fleet".
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 March 3; No. 2149
    Thanks for shoe strings, books, corset covers, and I owe you money. Stuart's visit. Riding habit and robe.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 March 9; No. 2150
    So pleased at your having a niece. Friends. Uncle in White House (so I can never say enough nice things about the Tafts).
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 March 17; No. 2151
    Telegram - "Here with Mrs. Flagler and wish you were here too".
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 April 1; No. 2152
    Telegram - requesting you send lace sleeves and pieces.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 April 18; No. 2153
    Having good time. Going to Washington and then Philadelphia. Godchild being christened.
  - A. Barrett & Sons to Miss Hare, 1909 May 10; No. 2154
    Bill for brushes, mirrors, etc.
  - George Douglas Krumbhaur to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 May 29; No. 2155
    Delighted with visit to you.
  - Bertha F. Beale (niece) to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 June 18; No. 2156
    Thank you for check and dresses.
  - E.F. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 June 28; No. 2157
    Recommendations of London cafes for luncheons, hiring carriage and doctors.
  - Maria Beale to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 July 1; No. 2158
    Thank you for dresses. Been in Washington and for two weeks read of past generations and still trying to get fresh evidence for your Colonial Dame paper. Would like to go to England and make pilgrimage to old castles and manors of ancestors.
  - Karl Urban to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 July 5; No. 2159
    In reference to accommodations.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 July 5; No. 2160
    Bon voyage note.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 July 7; No. 2161
    Magazine pictures, poems, cartoons, etc.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 July 7; No. 2162
    Marconigram - "Promptly deserted but safely home missing you terrible."
  - Stuart to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 July 7; No. 2163
    Marconigram - "Best possible good wishes for delightful trip."
  - Margaretta and Stuart to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 July 8; No. 2164
    Marconigram - "Here's good luck may you return full fledged abbaye heroine."
  - Rydie to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1909 July 13; No. 2165
    Thank you for dress for Maisie, your god-child. News of house and children.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 July 15; No. 2166
    News of home, family and friends.
  - Mrs. A.B. Kelley (Mariana) to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 July 16; No. 2167
    Bon voyage letter.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 July 22; No. 2168
    Will see you in Paris. Would like Connie to come be with me abroad.
  - _________ to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 July 22; No. 2169
    Fear there is little chance of my seeing you abroad.
  - Mitre Hotel to Mrs. Hare, 1909 July; No. 2170
  - Horace to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 July 26; No. 2171
    Order soft leather hunting boots from Peal & Co., and pink hunting coat from Jantz. Willing and I may go to Nova Scotia and Bar Harbor.
  - _________ to Miss E.B. Hare, 1909 July; No. 2172
    Sundry bills to be paid.
  - _________ to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 July; No. 2173
    Bills on European trip.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 August 3; No. 2174
    Airplane crossed channel and Wrights flying 50 miles an hour. Tariff settled. Horace returned from Virginia where he purchased a horse. C.C. Cuyler's death (motor overturned in south of France.) Home news.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 August 3; No. 2175
    Market St. disaster (?) Another volume of my book is finished. Burning of Snyder's barn and greenhouse. The children.
  - _________ to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 August 8; No. 2176
    Hotel bills. (European trip)
  - Rydie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 August 9; No. 2177
    The dress you made for Maisie "did up" beautifully. General family news.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 August 12; No. 2178
    Truxtun and I go to Nova Scotia and Horace will join us for fishing and sailing. On the household help and home news. Uncle Ned's been visiting and he's talking to Grandmama now.
  - T.T.H. to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 August 16; No. 2179
    Motor trip - car a great acquisition. Going to Nova Scotia with Willing. Katharine to go to Atlantic City. Having plans drawn for garage and chicken house.
  - M.R.C. to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 August 17; No. 2180
  - A. Zimmer to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 August 21; No. 2181
    In reference to reservation of rooms.
  - Maria to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 August 22; No. 2182
    Been to York Harbor with Hope and Lena. Left Lena there with Connie. Your Mother well and Willing looking after her. Madie looking at rooms on Spruce St. to spend winter in with Miss Homer. Viola at Harford (don't know what will be decided upon for her). Emily, Arthur, Ned, friends, deaths and Rydie's house.
  - M.M. to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 August 22; No. 2183
    Passage, itinerary, and this there a chance of seeing you in Paris?
  - W.H. Gaskell to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 August 23; No. 2184
    Sorry I missed you, but hope you can visit us on your way back.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 August 24; No. 2185
    Comments on your travels, news of household help, on arrangements for Viola and Madie and Connie away with Lena at York. Horace, Willing and Truxtun's proposed trip. Truxton's children. Social activities - dinners, luncheons, visitors, etc. On friends and family. Cass's plans.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 August 27; No. 2186
    Detained by work necessary from collapse of building, but will leave for Nova Scotia with Truxton and Horace soon.
  - Charles (brother) to Ned (Mr. Edward Beale), 1909 August 29; No. 2187
    Here after absence of 50 years. Will stop in Philadelphia to see you before going home. Enclosing old letters from H.B. Hare - invitation to a picnic, and request from Savannah to order New York Herald and other periodicals for him. Note from Emily.
  - Liberty & Co., Ltd. to Mrs. Hare, 1909 September 1; No. 2188
    Requesting instructions on where to send cloak purchased.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1909 September 5; No. 2189
    Cablegram - "All well here and Brookfield love from all to you both".
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 September 6; No. 2190
    Sailing with Dr. Hubert Norris. Description of place. Family news. Looking into purchase of house and boat here.
  - Horace to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1909 September 6; No. 2191
    Visit to Townsends and Nova Scotia. May buy boat and house here. Package in London - will you see it gets home? Horse for Esther.
  - The Gibson House to Mrs. Hare, 1909 September 7; No. 2192
  - Ridie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1909 September 9; No. 2193
    Mr. Brengel's dinner. Unsolicited order from the Press.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 September 10; No. 2194
    Comments on "your cure", Willing's trip, other family news, Mr. Meigs visits, household help, Charlie's visit (has written two long books), about purchases for me and about Henry Chapman's and General Corbin's deaths.
  - Mlle. Polak to Madame Hare, 1909 September 18; No. 2195
    Bill for clothes.
  - Douglas Krumbhaar to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1909 November 8; No. 2196
    Were so happy with your visit and glad you enjoyed it, but you were here in "Squaw Winter" which precedes "Indian Summer", and would have been so much nicer if weather was good. Comments on historic interest of trip you took down the Mohawk.
  - Bertha Montgomery to Cousin Emily, 1909 November 21; No. 2197
    Thank you for basket of fruit.
  - Grandmama to C. Willing Hare, 1909 November 27; No. 2198
    Thank you for violets for Thanksgiving.
  - Helen S. Hoffman to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1909 December 10; No. 2199
    Sorry to miss seeing you when you called. Even with her faults, have engaged Anna.
  - M.M. to Mrs. Hare, 1909 December 18; No. 2200
    Thank you fo handkerchief case.
  - Advertisement, 1910; No. 2201
    "Passion Play at Oberammergau".
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 January 25; No. 2202
    Friendly letter - requesting favors, etc.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 January 27; No. 2203
    Want you to come February 1. Comments on Mr. Wright and coats. Sent money for candy. Enclosed picture of Christine Norman (playing in "Israel").
  - The Lehigh Coal & Navigation Co. to Emily P. Hare, 1910 March 12; No. 2204
    In reference to Lehigh Stock.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 March 26; No. 2205
    Telegram - Easter greetings.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 March 28; No. 2206
    Telegram - thanks for Easter eggs.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 April 1; No. 2207
    Telegram - hope to see you before end of April.
  - C. Willing Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 April 2; No. 2208
    Fishing. Enjoying this place and people here.
  - George Douglas Krumbhaar to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 May 11; No. 2209
    Invitation to you and Mrs. Bayard to visit Cazenovia next week. Bring your habit - have a fine, safe mount for you.
  - Charles (brother) to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 May 20; No. 2210
    General family news.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 June 7; No. 2211
    Everything in New York seems so changed since landing. Invitation for you to visit. Family, friends, and plans for summer.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1910 August 11; No. 2212
    Blowing too hard for us to venture out fishing.
  - T.T.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 12; No. 2213
    Description of cottage. Katharine and children, tennis, bathing, sailing, and silver cigarette case containing $35. dropped overboard.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 August 18; No. 2214
    Jessie's death (had been with us for 30 years).
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 18; No. 2215
    Daily routine. Created excitement at luncheon by wearing new purple "wrapper". Social activities - dinners, dances, visitors, music, etc. Description of hotel. Connie's activities. Friends and family. Truxtun and family's mishaps on vacation. Drive with Ned and Maria. Edmund Lewis' death. Charles' voyage to Canada, and he is much better.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 22; No. 2216
    Postcard informing everything well and letter must be delayed.
  - Hannah M. Chapman to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 23; No. 2217
    Invitation to you to visit in September.
  - Mary Helen Cadwalader to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 24; No. 2218
    John's been ill (even thought it might be typhoid). Family and friends. Motor cars. Hare relative met by Kate in Bath, England.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 25; No. 2219
    About correspondence. Charlie's journey to Canada and around New York (went to "Airation Meet" at which parachutist was killed). Connie's visit to Drifton. Melba is here at Inn - singing into some Grafaphone "Victor" for which she gets $1000. Daisy and Viola Beale at Dog Show. "Guir House" by my son (Charles) Visit to Ned's to see Charlie. Visitors - Jennie Cassatt and Maria.
  - Marian Mott to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 August 29; No. 2220
    Six visits in six weeks (traveled by motor). Friends and family. Discouraging news about trolley.
  - Hannah Chapman to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 August 31; No. 2221
    Delighted you are coming. McLeans, Mrs. Walsh and Emily.
  - Beckie Spencer to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 September 2; No. 2222
    Thanks for good words for Welling to your cousin M. Bakhmeteff (she and her husband so kind to him). Russia and its surprises.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 September 3; No. 2223
    Delightful summer. Grandmama well. Automobile ready - am looking for chauffeur.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1910 September 7; No. 2224
    Declining invitation to visit Harford this autumn. His Canadian trip and disappointed could not see you and accept Willings invitation.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 September 14; No. 2225
    Dinner with Willing and Horace. Horace's visit on Sunday - took C. as far as "Old Radnor Church". Sunday before we went to Ardmore Church. News of friends, postcards, Truxtun and family and social engagements.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 September 20; No. 2226
    Waiting in bathing suit for H. Bathing, sailing, tea, etc. While sailing on "Venture", the mast broke off - had to be taken home and send motor boat for boat. H. has given up moose shooting and Ben agreeable guest.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 September 26; No. 2227
    Not home to welcome you, but invite you to use our box at the Horse Show.
  - M.M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 September 27; No. 2228
    Glad you are coming in October. Comments on motor cars and politics (hates T. Roosevelt).
  - Mary P. Mitchell to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1910 September 29; No. 2229
    Trust trolley may be far away and automobiles may only be a scare.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 September 30; No. 2230
    Your luncheon, grandson, Katharine, and wants Connie to visit. Madam Hayes (nearly 100 years old), and the rest of the family, friends - Eugenia Stein and Laura Edwards. Undecided living plans.
  - Maria M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1910 September 30; No. 2231
    Discussing proposed trolley line (trying to convince it may not be too bad).
  - Hannah M. Chapman to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 October 2; No. 2232
    Friends all leaving Bar Harbor.
  - Charles Fearon & Co., 1910 October 11; No. 2233
    Statement on sale of Pennsylvania Railroad stock.
  - Longacre & Ewing to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1910 October 11; No. 2234
    Personal property fire insurance policy for 120 S. 22nd St.
  - Wayne Fox to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 November 22; No. 2235
    Receipt for $5.00.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1910 December 1; No. 2236
    Declining invitation to visit. Working on literary work and orchard.
  - Mrs. Andrew Sullivan to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1910 December 25; No. 2237
    To thank you, Esther and Willing for Christmas gifts (dolls, toys, turkey, cranberries, oranges, etc.)
  - Wayne MacVeagh to Miss Hare, 1910 December 26; No. 2238
    Received gifts and want you to come.
  - Betty Sinclair Lyon to Miss Esther Hare, 1910 December 27; No. 2239
    Thank you for Christmas gift - Munich box. Going to hospital in Philadelphia - to have throat cut.
  - Nora to Miss Hare, 1910 December 28; No. 2240
    Thank you for Christmas cable.
  - Margaretta and Wayne MacVeagh to Miss Esther Hare, 1911; No. 2241
    Telegrams - (no particular news - wishes, asking for favors, thank yous, etc.)
  - Charles to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1911 January 3; No. 2242
    Thank you for gifts - gold coin, tie and studs.
  - Mary Boytin to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1911 January 10; No. 2243
    In reference to book - family history.
  - Wayne MacVeagh to Miss Hare, 1911 January 23; No. 2244
  - Wayne MacVeagh to Miss Hare, 1911 March 6; No. 2245
    Thank you for Valentine remembrance.
  - Rydie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1911 April 25; No. 2246
    Thank you for most generous gift for our trip. (Mailing directions).
  - The Garden Club of Philadelphia, 1911 April 27; No. 2247
    Garden Club news.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1911 May 8; No. 2248
    Mother ill.
  - Charlton Yarnall to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1911 May 20; No. 2249
    Thank you for your letter (death of Agnes).
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 July 22; No. 2250
    Journey there and description of cottage.
  - Maria M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1911 August 10; No. 2251
    Your letter to Vienna never reached me. Houseful of people. Suggestion you take empty house at Drifton and bring Mrs. Beale. Request you give me names of anyone who works for the benefit of women.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 August 18; No. 2252
    Bathing, social engagements and Aunt C.'s plans.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 September 2; No. 2253
    My luncheon. Willing and Horace's activities. Aunt C. and Grandma. Maggie returned and working out well. Motored to Wayne and brought Maria back to tea.
  - Maria to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 September 3; No. 2254
    Went to meet steamer - baby safely at home. Want your help for Lena's wedding. Going to see Mama and Connie.
  - E.F.B. (brother) to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1911 September 8; No. 2255
    Better than when you left. Think Mother is improving.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 September 9; No. 2256
    Sunbathed on your balcony. Shopping requests. Ned and Maria, (Truxtun Beale and his boy visiting them).
  - Mary C. Mitchell to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1911 October 5; No. 2257
  - ________ to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1911 October 7; No. 2258
    Nonsense for Americans to go to Europe. Mamie coming. Surprised with Beale wedding invitation.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1911 December 7; No. 2259
    About coming to Philadelphia. News of Bakhmeteff's, Nora and Percy Farrar (rotten).
  - M.M. to Mrs. Hare, 1911 December 25; No. 2260
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1911 September 21; No. 2260a
    House, Grandma B, on your going to Mrs. Tuckerman's (could return with Willing who is going away). Katharine and children returned. Horace busy with Hunt and Horse Show.
  - H. Mercer to Mrs. Hare, 1911 November 2; No. 2260b
    Everything goes on allright.
  - Mary Pederson to Mrs. Hare, 1911 December 23; No. 2260c
    Thank you - received coats, but too small, could I exchange them.
  - Mother to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1911 December 26; No. 2261
    Thanks to all of you for lovely Christmas gifts.
  - Wayne MacVeagh to Miss Hare, 1911 December 30; No. 2262
  - Horace to Miss Hare, 1912 January 5; No. 2263
    Bouquet of orchids from J.J. Habermehl's Sons (florist)
  - M.E. Powel to Emily, 1912 February 9; No. 2264
    In reference to letters of General and Mrs. Washington (purely friendly and nothing interesting to Carnegie Institute).
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1912 February 19; No. 2265
    Request you get Mother's handkerchiefs and other things. Telegram - best wishes on your journey.
  - Richard R. Neill to Mrs. Horace Hare, 1912 February 19; No. 2266
    Bon voyage note, enclosing cards of introduction.
  - Charles Teixeira & Co. to H.B. Hare, 1912 February 28; No. 2267
    Bill for furniture and baskets.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1912 March 1; No. 2268
    Friendly letter - social activities and church work. Hope you get audience with Pope, and others you should see.
  - Hotel Bristol to C.W. Hare, 1912 March 7; No. 2269
  - Mother to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 March 12; No. 2270
    Visits, sights, friends here and about apartment when you come.
  - ________ to Mrs. Hare, 1912; No. 2271
    Calling cards and invitations. (Rome)
  - M.M. to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1912 March 19; No. 2272
    Jacky and Grace visiting me. Spent two weeks in Boston and Concord. Everyone not going to Italy are taking Panama trips. Suffrage movement very lively. Will you march in parade in New York?
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1912 March 21; No. 2273
    Household help most satisfactory. Given no parties, just dined a few times with friends, and quite "sick of my corner of the world".
  - Mother to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 March 22; No. 2274
    Change in Rome (fear Willing will not like it). Invited Walter Lowrie to lunch. About rooms.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1912 March 22; No. 2275
    Weather, children, Katharine and animals. Late for dinner with Snowden's because motor got stuck in mud.
  - Horace to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 March 25; No. 2276
    Explanation of reason for not writing (home news disturbing to those on journey).
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1912 March 25; No. 2277
    Returning by train to Rome - engage rooms and carriage. Met Pattersons from Washington - going on excursion with them. Norrises very attentive - through them met pleasant English people.
  - Grand Hotel Metropole to Miss Hare, 1912 March 29; No. 2278
  - Mariana to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 March 29; No. 2279
    First year of Bert's new venture. On friends and children. Have "fever" to learn to drive automobile.
  - Constance to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1912 April 2; No. 2280
    Grandma can only get motor rarely as Horace uses it every day. Visitors. If you can - get a hat for me.
  - Katharine to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 April 6; No. 2281
    Finger well again. Children. Rarely see Horace. Had Willing's car to go to dinner of Andrew Gray's, also went to dinners at Snowden's and Pepper's.
  - Grandmama to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 April 8; No. 2282
    Comments on your travels, and your Great Grandmother Hare's experience in Madeira. Visitors and news of friends and family. Rarely see Horace. Motor drives. Dr. Musser's death.
  - Thomas R. Elcock, Jr. to Mr. Hare, 1912 April 15; No. 2283
    Business news, (have been representing you, and on advertising). Changes in high offices of company Theodore Roosevelt carried Pennsylvania in primaries. Politics.
  - T.T.H. to C. Willing Hare, 1912 April 15; No. 2284
    Roosevelt swept primaries of Pennsylvania. Auto accident which killed Hoffman and Ryerson - Ryerson's parents returned on disastrous Titanic. Tom Smith escaped from Junior Republic.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1912 April 17; No. 2285
    Surrounded by flowers (Easter gifts). Family activities. Visits by family and friends. Connie feeling miserable. Comments on your travels. Connie's social engagements. Truxtun visited. Katharine in mourning for uncle. Dr. Musser's death. Mrs. McKane's death. Auto accident killing Lewis Hoffman and Arthur Ryerson. Visit from Horace. Thank you for scarf. Awful news of Titanic (Mr. Ryerson missing).
  - Molly Baltz to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 April 21; No. 2286
    Titanic (Mr. John Thayer missing). Newspaper article "Mrs. Thayer's Story of Wreck".
  - Esther Hare to _______, 1912 April; No. 2287
    (Batch of letters) Copy of thank you to Walter. To Miss MacVeagh on travels. One to Horace, and notes.
  - Walter Lowrie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 April 22; No. 2288
    Invitations and thank yous.
  - Tax Collector to Constance R. Beale, 1912 April 26; No. 2289
    Receipt for taxes.
  - ________ to H.B. Hare, 1912 May 4; No. 2290
    Bill of lading - Pennsylvania Railroad (10 packages willow furniture), and bill for duties.
  - Scipio Borghese to Miss C. Willing Hare, 1912 May 6; No. 2291
    Enclosed card for three seats (Sunday morning service at St. Peters). Offering services for sightseeing, introductions, etc.
  - Constance to Mrs. Horace Hare, 1912 May 9; No. 2292
    Social events - dinner to meet the French delegation (Christening of boat), and received at the "R" mansion. Shopping you can do for me.
  - T.T. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1912 May 9; No. 2293
    Titanic tragedy. Children. Have been to Hot Springs for week. Have decided to sublet our cottage at Winter Harbor. Social news - Ben Chew's marriage to Ann Thomson and Tom Ridgeway's engagement to Miss Wayne. Those having babies.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1912 May 12; No. 2294